# BRYAN DULOG, CFA, FRM

Relocating to Tampa, FL (646) 404-1692 • <u>bryan.dulog.2@gmail.com</u>

### **SUMMARY**

Financial services professional and MBA candidate with over 12 years of experience in the banking sector, risk management, capital and liquidity expertise, corporate finance, leading and coordinating teams, analytical ability, financial analysis, problem solving, data analysis, financial modeling, financial reporting and extensive financial product knowledge.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Department of the Treasury – Office of the Comptroller of the Currency Large Bank Examiner

New York, NY June 2014 - Present

- **Financial Planning & Analysis:** Evaluated earnings for a \$1 trillion bank to support internal ratings and determine quality and composition of earnings results. Reviewed quarterly financial statements, accounting and budgeting processes and management reports to identify trends and linkages with strategic plan, capital plan, divestitures and planned growth.
- **Finance and Treasury:** Regularly meet and facilitate Q&A with Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Treasurer of a \$100 billion bank to discuss quarterly profit and loss, balance sheet budgeting, capital forecasts and new products.
- **Data and Reporting:** Evaluate enterprise data, reporting, data aggregation, data transformation to measure data quality at a \$1 trillion bank for regulatory evaluation.
- Quantitative Analysis: Review statistical models used to measure and forecast risk weighted assets and quantify
  operational risk to ensure reasonableness of assumptions and accuracy of capital requirements. Led review of regression
  models used for stress testing and presented conclusions to OCC senior leaders and senior bank executives.
- Capital Planning Analysis: Review and evaluate financial and management reports to support ratings of capital, stress
  testing, recovery planning and quality of risk management practices. Conduct analysis of capital levels, trends, sensitivity
  and scenario analysis, dividend history, and other metrics to determine the sufficiency of capital given a bank's risk profile.
- Cross Functional Collaboration: Successfully improved feedback timelines by coordinating periodic review of material changes to Basel III capital models with internal stakeholders and other regulatory agencies.

KPMG Risk Consultant New York, NY October 2010 – May 2014

- **Strategic M&A**: Assisted in the acquisition of a \$2 billion bank by evaluating potential regulatory implications, capital related GAAP disclosures, credit risk, staffing levels, board oversight and strategic planning.
- **Financial and Regulatory Reporting:** Reconciled general ledger system amounts to regulatory reporting line items in order to ensure accuracy of reporting and to prevent operational risk losses for a large investment banking client.
- **Data Cleansing and Management:** Utilized Excel pivot tables and vlookups to sort, cleanse and classify operational risk data for loading into a bank client's proprietary risk system.
- Client Management: Clients include Goldman Sachs, Bank of America, Fannie Mae, BNY Mellon, Everbank & PNC.

### Department of the Treasury – Office of Thrift Supervision Bank Examiner

Jersey City, NJ July 2008 - October 2010

• **Financial Analysis:** Conducted financial analysis of banks with \$100-600 million in assets. Evaluated capital levels, funding profiles, asset/liability composition and earnings. Presented conclusions to bank senior management and board of directors.

#### **EDUCATION**

Carnegie Mellon University – Tepper School of Business Master of Business Administration Pittsburgh, PA Expected May 2022

Memberships: Alpha Club, Graduate Finance Society, Business & Technology Club, and Data Analytics Club

Baruch College – Zicklin School of Business Bachelor of Business Administration

New York, NY May 2008

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Professional Certifications: Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA) & Financial Risk Manager (FRM)
- Affiliations: CFA Society New York, Global Association of Risk Professionals
- Volunteerism: Treasurer of 68 East Hartsdale Avenue Corporation
- Software/Programming: Bloomberg, Reuters, Tableau, Advanced Microsoft Excel, Python, R, SQL, HTML